啊我赢我啊啊啊啊天啊啊哈哈哈哈哈哈哈
啊刷新了我的世界观
快的电车我做过很多
但两秒投的成绩
一闭眼一睁眼结束了
而且你知道吗
他是实打实两秒投的成绩
但你进三秒内啊
每0.1秒都是一件很可怕的提升
你知道他为什么会有这么快
因为它有1034匹
而且超过了1200牛米
而且呢很重要的是
因为它后面呢是有两个档位变速箱的
所以它在起步的时候呢
可以用更低的档位
把这个扭矩更夸张的放大
你知道他纽北可以做什么成绩吗
7分07秒五
这个是非常夸张
就在以前啊
大家都觉得这可能是911的高端车型
才能做到的成绩
现在没想到一台普普通通的四门电动车
可以做到了普普通通啊
那不普通吧
因为它毕竟后座是拆除了
既然这台车这么硬核的话呢
我觉得吧乔乔上车
我来带你走一次
新疆咸鱼居然能掉到无敌
你
哇哇滴哇哈哈哈哇哈哈哈哈
我骑在沙上的吗
哦吼哇那个动能回收我往后的狂
我的天哇哦哇哦哇哦哇哇哇哇呵呵
你看我头发太快了
哇哇哇
你是不是有点hold不住啊
王总大家都说开车呢人要比车凶
就是我觉得我是我真的把持不住
但不要紧啊
我给你找来了一位专业人士
应该没有人开台看比他更专业的吧
Hello
Hey
Nice meet you
I think i cannot handle this car
So i will hand over the baby to you pressing somebody with this carit's a pretty easy task
Okay
Let me take you
Ok
Hello
Nice to meet you nice to meet you ha ha ha ha
王总大哥是谁啊啊
他是普普通通的一位德国司机
哈啊
这台台看的记录呢
七分零七也是他做的
you not跟那狗
Really really fast
No
Really gentle
Okay
As you can imagine
You know a ha ha
不two烟酒店从来不干
672 14节出林墨镜人都跟他买好了
打开机表里变个人
看错来错嘞
啊啊啊
Oh my god
So how do you like the taa ha ha ha
Let me just catch my breath
Ha ha ha wow
You make it lost super
Easy
Ha ha ha
It is super easy
I just jumped in like cold tires
Whatever you just go it
Does feels like a race car
Yeah
Electric vehicle
It's not the lightest car in the world
But the suspension really overcompensates
That feels supernatural
It always levels the car
So it's always kind of horizontal
I mean it just makes everything
So much easier and so much more control
You just jump in you just go
太吓人了
你知道吗
原来人在最害怕的时候是叫不出来声音的
这台车就像一个吸铁石一样
吸在地上就这么巨
它好像好不费力就跑成这样
有没有想过他可能在纽北河
在这个赛道里跑了比人家模拟器还多的圈速呢
How many laps have you done in nb
Uh
Pretty sure
It's thousands of lives
Thousands of los
Yeah uh
What's the difference about driving
A electric car in a petrol car
Do you think it's more challenging from the beginning
I've never have been real fan of electric cars
Okay
But the more
I drive them and the more
I also see the technical benefits of the cars
I really like it
Because it like combines both worlds
It can be super luxury quiet easy chilled
But then you just switch the nop and within a second
It's drives like a race
Carry like honest for me
That's at me at a minute for me
It's the best porsche
Okay
Thank you
So much for your time
You're welcome
I see you very soon
Let's see him in the next episode
哇哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈哈